[{"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 19, "question": "Angie, can you hear me?", "qSentId": 18}, {"answer": "Well, (speaking in foreign language).", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "But do you know which one it was?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Did she say that?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Well, no, because we never -- well, I never saw these girls.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "And do you know if there were any other children in the house that these women were being kept?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "Did you know what he did for a living?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "He's like a 50-year-old man.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "What kind of man was he?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 69, "question": "Did you speak to him?", "qSentId": 68}, {"answer": "She just say the phone.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "When Amanda Berry ran into your aunt's house, did she say anything?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "And then she used the phone herself to call the police, is that right?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "Well, that was quick.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 88, "question": "And how long did it take the police to get to your house?", "qSentId": 87}, {"answer": "I don't think not even -- a minute, I think.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "So a few minutes?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Well, the thing is that they didn't believe at first.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "And what happened then?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "Did your aunt see the other women being brought out of the house?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "Really bad.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "And what kind of condition was Amanda Berry in, did your aunt say?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "No, my aunt is crying because she said she couldn't believe so many years living here and never notice nothing suspicious.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "Your aunt is crying or Amanda Berry was crying?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 114, "question": "But we didn't know much about Michelle Knight but the other two girls had been the subject of many vigils by their families, is that right?", "qSentId": 113}, {"answer": "Well, she said the last one that came out of the house, it was a girl, she might have been like 10 years old.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "And did your aunt see the other women coming out of the property after the police arrived?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Is that your understanding?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "And has your aunt now given a statement to the police?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "It really is.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "This is a really extraordinary story, isn't it?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "I'm overjoyed.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "How does it make you feel, having been through something like this as a parent, when you hear about something like this?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Well, I don't have a lot of experience in the reunification process, but I can assure you they'll need to be tested medically, they will need to undergo I would imagine some intense psychological counseling for a very long period of time, because they will have a lot of different conflicting thoughts going through their minds.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "And given all your experience in these kind of cases, what would be the most pressing and urgent things that these young women as they are now will have to go through in terms of readapting back to normal life?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "Piers, it's incredible.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "John, this is really quite extraordinary, isn't it?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "Well, John said it many times.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "What do you make of that?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Well, what I can tell you is that it's almost like a carnival atmosphere on the street.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "What can you tell me about the latest on it?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "Well, I think so.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "But was the general feeling that they must be dead, that it had been so long with no real leads, that was the only conclusion people could reach?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "I need police.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "You need police, fire or ambulance?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "I've been kidnapped and I've been with him for ten years and I'm here, I'm free now.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "What's going on there?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "I can't hear you.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "What's your address?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "Hello?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "NIDENTIFIED MALE: As soon as we get a car open.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "Are they on their way right now?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "His name is --", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Who's the guy you're -- who's the guy who went out?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "He's like 52.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "How old is he?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "He's Hispanic.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "Is he white, black or Hispanic?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "I don't know, because he's not here right now.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "What's he wearing?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "The police are on the way.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "Who knows?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Talk to them when they get there, OK?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "I was in a business meeting and I got a 911 text call, my cousin.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "And Sylvia?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "I do not.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Do you know, Sheila, the reaction of Gina's mother when she heard the news?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "They never did.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Sylvia, did the family ever give up hope that one day Gina would be found alive?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "IGARO: It is amazing.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "It really is truly remarkable, isn't it?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "It's a confirmation that, in fact, Amanda Berry has a child.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "I need police.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "You need police, fire or ambulance?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "I've been kidnapped and I've been with him for ten years and I'm here, I'm free now.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "What's going on there?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "I can't hear you.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "What's your address?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "Hello?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "As soon as we get a car open.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "Are they on their way right now?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "His name is --", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "Who's the guy you're -- who's the guy who went out?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "He's like 52.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 544, "question": "How old is he?", "qSentId": 543}, {"answer": "He's Hispanic.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Is he white, black or Hispanic?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "I don't know, because he's not here right now.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "What's he wearing?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "The police are on the way.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "Who knows?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "Talk to them when they get there, OK?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "Well, absolutely.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Tell me this, is there likely to be criticism of the police and the other investigators, that all of these girls have been found 10 years later, literally right under the noses of the investigators, a few blocks from where they disappeared?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "I can't go into any further specific details.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 673, "question": "Is there any indication they were restrained where they were held?", "qSentId": 672}, {"answer": "I can't go into any further specific details.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "Can you comment on that?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "Again, I'm sorry, I can't go into any further specific details.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "Did she feel any pain anywhere?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "Again, I can't really go into any further specific details.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 688, "question": "Can you talk about their mental state?", "qSentId": 687}, {"answer": "Again, I can't go into any further specific details at the moment.", "docId": "130506pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "Are family members with them?", "qSentId": 696}]